## **CONTACT**

140 Middle Street Apt. 1 Manchester, NH 03101 (774) 364-1531 jay.hanaford@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/jasonhanaford http://jayhanaford.com

#### WHAT I OFFER:

Web Design
Print Design
Logo Design
Illustration
Icon Design
Brand Identity
Packaging Design
Layout Design Concept
Multimedia Design
User Interface Design
Flash Integration

#### **AWARDS**

Graphic Communications Award of academic excellence and service

High Honors Award in the area of Graphic Communication

Alpha Chi National College Honor Scholarship Society Inductee

Gold Key received at Scholastic Art Awards student art show

# JASON HANAFORD

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a graphic designer specializing in web design, print design, corporate identity and branding. I create clean, creative, and functional designs. I am very passionate, organized, and focused with my work.

I am a perfectionist, but I always consider time as an important factor. My experience has given me the ability to easily adapt from being a designer, to coder, to decision maker. My adaptability shows that I can handle any task I'm given whether it be print, branding, multimedia, or web.

#### **CAREER HISTORY**

Audio Amateur Inc. – May 2005 to present Graphic Director

Oversee the art direction of the graphics department. Design concepts, identity, execution, and presentation of numerous projects: a monthly subscription-based magazine, two business-to-business periodicals, website design, books, interface design, direct-mail packages, magazine advertisements, web advertisements, product catalogues, and company branding. Some highlights include:

- Design and development of the company website which includes e-commerce and other interactive material.
   Designed with (X)HTML, CSS, and Javascript.
- See http://audioamateurinc.com, http://www.audioxpress.com, http://voicecoilmagazine.com
- Created Flash-based digital editions of our magazines for use on the PC, Mac, iPad, and the Android OS.
- Updated the company identity. Modern design concepts were utilized for the overall layout and production of magazines, in-house advertisements, company branding, and website.
- Saved thousands of dollars per year in production costs by researching alternatives.

FIDF – April 2010 to June 2010 Web Designer

Design for implementation of site content throughout. See http://fidf.org

Freelance Graphic Designer - June 2004 to present

Provide identity, print, and web design for a variety of clients. Select work:

- RyanSobol.com (In Progress) Website design, logo design, site implementation
- The MacDowell Colony High-quality brochure and poster design
- Fiveumbrellas Website design for a San Francisco start-up company

### **EDUCATION**

Franklin Pierce University – Rindge, NH Bachelor of Arts, Graphic Communications Magna cum Laude. Minor in Fine Arts

#### **SKILLS**

HTML, XHTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Abobe Creative Suite 5.5 (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Dreamweaver, Flash, Fireworks, Acrobat Professional), QuarkXpress, Textmate, Firebug, SEO Techniques, Google Analytics, Google AdSense, Email Marketing, Familiar with GitHub, Familiar with Heroku, Amazon S3, Zmag and 3D Issue, Digital Photography, Microsoft Office XP, Microsoft Windows 7, Mac OS X Snow Leopard